They made scuba suits for cockroaches
and you need to see why. So it turns out
scientists have found a way to remotely
control cockroaches by putting
electrodes in their body. And they're
notoriously hardy creatures, so the goal
is to eventually attach cameras and have
them search for people in disaster zones
or hard-to-reach places. But some
disaster zones involve flooding and
cockroaches can't survive underwater. So
they made them [music] 3D printed
watertight scuba suits that connect to
their air holes and give them air. So
now the cockroach with its scuba suit
can move around in the water for hours
at a time and they have an even bigger
goal, which is to make them
>> [laughter]
>> space suits so they can help us [music]
explore other planets. If you want to
see that, subscribe.